(Mary:)Oh, it's my pleasure. Mm.
(Mary:)I'm so glad y'all could make it.
(Mary:)So, tell me,
what's going on back home?
(Amy:)Well, uh, Howard and Bernadette
had their baby.
Oh, that's wonderful!
(Mary:)Now, have they decided
to raise it Jewish or regular?
(Sheldon:)Welcome to Texas.
(Amy:)They haven't said.
(Amy:)Anyway, we, uh, we also have
(Amy:)some exciting news to share.
(Sheldon:)Oh, wait, wait...
I... Shouldn't we just eat?
(Sheldon:)You know, I mean, God did take
time out of his busy schedule
(Sheldon:)to bless these Sloppy Joes.
(Mary:)Come on, Shelly,
tell me your news.
(Sheldon:)All right. This is on you.
(Sheldon:)Amy and I are living together
in sin,
(Sheldon:)like a couple of New Yorkers.
(Sheldon:)Now, while you scold us, I'm
going to get a knife and a fork.
(Sheldon:)Joe may be sloppy,
but Sheldon's not.
(Mary:)Well, thank you
for letting me know,